[
    {
        "title": "hej",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM0",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM1",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM2",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM3",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM4",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?0",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 0,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "hej",
        "cards": [],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 1,
        "progress": [
            {
                "right": 0,
                "questions": 0,
                "date": "2018-12-10 16:00:58"
            },
            {
                "right": 0,
                "questions": 0,
                "date": "2018-12-10 16:01:14"
            }
        ],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "hej",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM0",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM1",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM2",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM3",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM4",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?2",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 2,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "hej",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM0",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM1",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM2",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM3",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM4",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?3",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 3,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "hej",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM0",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM1",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM2",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM3",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "answer": "JA DE ÄR DOM4",
                "text": "ÄR APOR FINA?4",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 4,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "Mattias",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "är mattias cool?",
                "answer": "svar nej",
                "text": "är mattias cool?",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "varför inte?",
                "answer": "han e ävkogt",
                "text": "varför inte?",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            },
            {
                "question": "azerbajan",
                "answer": "sickdude",
                "text": "azerbajan",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 6,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "axel",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "azerbajan",
                "answer": "yes againg dude",
                "text": "azerbajan",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 7,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "einar",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "hejsan",
                "answer": "tja",
                "text": "hejsan",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 8,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "Sixten",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "e han ful",
                "answer": "nej han e söt",
                "text": "e han ful",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 9,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    },
    {
        "title": "Teo",
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "hur mår markus",
                "answer": "bra",
                "text": "hur mår markus",
                "shouldShowAnswer": false
            }
        ],
        "completed": [],
        "currentCard": 0,
        "id": 10,
        "progress": [],
        "wrongs": 0
    }
]